<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 2017-08-08 오후 9:54:43 -->
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag='TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CJGG_ROCKCAFE_DESC'>
			<Text>Rockcafe</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag='TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CJGG_ROCKCAFE_STRATEGY'>
			<Text>Unique building of the Choujuu Gigaku. Replaces the Opera House. It provides 1 Musician Slot.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag='TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CJGG_ROCKCAFE_HELP'>
			<Text>Unique building of the Choujuu Gigaku. Replaces the Opera House. It provides 1 Musician Slot.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag='TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CJGG_ROCKCAFE_PEDIA'>
			<Text>Hard Rock Cafe Inc. is a chain of theme restaurants founded in 1971 by Isaac Tigrett and Peter Morton in London. In 1979, the cafe began covering its walls with rock and roll memorabilia, a tradition which expanded to others in the chain. In 2007, Hard Rock was sold to the Seminole Tribe of Florida, and since then it is headquartered in Orlando, Florida. As of December 2015, there were 191 Hard Rock locations in 59 countries, including 168 cafes, 23 hotels, and 11 casinos.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag='TXT_KEY_UNIT_CJGG_SINGER_DESC'>
			<Text>Singer</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag='TXT_KEY_UNIT_CJGG_SINGER_HELP'>
			<Text>Replaces Scout. Can perform Concert Tour and never obsolete.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag='TXT_KEY_UNIT_CJGG_SINGER_STRATEGY'>
			<Text>The night sparrow is a folk legend in western Japan. According to legend, if you're out at midnight, the night sparrow will follow you while singing "Chin Chin." The appearance of a night sparrow is a prodigious sign that you will meet a wolf/stray dog soon. Legend also has it that if you catch the night sparrow, you'll suffer from severe night-blindness.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag='TXT_KEY_UNIT_CJGG_SINGER_PEDIA'>
			<Text>Mystia Lorelei is a night sparrow with an outgoing egocentric personality, at least she sounds arrogant, that enjoys infusing confusion and terror into the hearts of humans using her ability: a song that creates confusion in those who hear her. Her song seems to attract nearby monsters as well. She roams the Youkai Trail near the Human Village that Keine Kamishirasawa tries to protect, in search of humans to frighten. She is indeed feared by the locals as people around her become blinded by darkness. Some time later, along with Kyouko Kasodani, they formed a duo combination called Choujuu Gigaku.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag='TXT_KEY_UNIT_CJGG_RANGER_DESC'>
			<Text>Ranger</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag='TXT_KEY_UNIT_CJGG_RANGER_HELP'>
			<Text>Replaces Composite Bowman. Ignores terrain cost and barrage I promotion.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag='TXT_KEY_UNIT_CJGG_RANGER_STRATEGY'>
			<Text>The United States Forest Service (USFS) is an agency of the U.S. Department of Agriculture that administers the nation's 154 national forests and 20 national grasslands, which encompass 193 million acres (780,000 km2).</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag='TXT_KEY_UNIT_CJGG_RANGER_PEDIA'>
			<Text>A park ranger, park warden, or forest ranger is a person entrusted with protecting and preserving parklands – national, state, provincial, or local parks. "Parks" may be broadly defined by some systems in this context, and include protected culturally or historically important built environments, and is not limited to the natural environment. Different countries use different names for the position. Warden is the favored term in Canada, Ireland, and the United Kingdom. Within the United States, the National Park Service refers to the position as a park ranger. The U.S. Forest Service refers to the position as a forest ranger. Other countries use the term park warden or game warden to describe this occupation. The profession includes a number of disciplines and specializations, and park rangers are often required to be proficient in more than one.</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
	<Language_ko_KR>
		<Row Tag='TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CJGG_ROCKCAFE_DESC'>
			<Text>락카페</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag='TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CJGG_ROCKCAFE_STRATEGY'>
			<Text>90년대 초반부터 중반까지 존재했던 곳. 말하자면 클럽의 프로토타입. 절대로 록밴드가 라이브로 연주하는 클럽이 아니다.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag='TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CJGG_ROCKCAFE_HELP'>
			<Text>조수기악의 고유 건물입니다. 오페라 극장을 대체하며 음악가 슬롯 1개를 제공합니다.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag='TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CJGG_ROCKCAFE_PEDIA'>
			<Text>90년대 들어서면서 당국의 유흥업소 탄압이 강화되고 높은 세금이 책정되면서 중소형 나이트클럽이 문을 닫게된다.[3] 7~80년대부터 나이트클럽은 대형화, 기업화 되었고, 웬만한 돈으로는 나이트클럽을 세울 수 없게 된 것. 이러한 문제 때문에 편법으로 등장한 나이트클럽이 락카페다. 일종의 90년대 한정판 나이트클럽. 락카페는 높은 세율을 피하기 위해, 그리고 일반적으로 유흥업소에 끼어드는 조폭등의 이권개입을 피하기 위해, 경찰의 지속적인 개입과 간섭을 피하기 위해 일반음식점으로 분류가 되어있었다. 때문에 경찰단속이 뜨면 실내등을 켜고 음악을 잔잔한것으로 바꾸고 모든 손님들이 순식간에 착석하는 기적(...)을 볼 수 있었다. 영화 비상구가 없다에 잘 나와있다.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag='TXT_KEY_UNIT_CJGG_SINGER_DESC'>
			<Text>가수</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag='TXT_KEY_UNIT_CJGG_SINGER_HELP'>
			<Text>정찰병을 대신합니다. 순회공연이 가능하며, 도태되지 않습니다.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag='TXT_KEY_UNIT_CJGG_SINGER_STRATEGY'>
			<Text>에히메 현의 우와지마 지방에 나타난다고 하는 요괴 참새의 일종. 말 그대로 밤길에 나타나서 “짹짹”하고 울음소리를 낸다. 웬일인가 의아해하고 있는 사이에 그 숫자는 점점 늘어가는데 삿갓이나 소매, 기모노의 옷자락 속에서도 울음소리가 들리게 된다. 거기다 주위에는 모기 같은 게 수없이 나타나서 길을 가는 것도 힘들어진다고 한다. 하지만 그 이상 큰 해가 미치는 것도 아니라서 마음을 가라앉히고 있으면 없어져버린다고 한다.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag='TXT_KEY_UNIT_CJGG_SINGER_PEDIA'>
			<Text>동방영야초 2면보스. 곁다리희생자 9호. 요스즈메라 불리는 요괴. 이는 노랫소리가 참새와 비슷해서 부르는 것으로, 밤에만 활동하는 데다 부가적인 능력인 '사람을 야맹증으로 만드는 능력' 때문에 외양을 보지 못해서 붙은 이름. 게임에서는 미스티아와의 전투중 플레이어 기체를 중심으로 해서 시계가 점점 좁아지는 것으로 구현되어 있다. 미스티아가 부르는 노래는 성인 로렐라이(Lorelei)에서 알 수 있듯이 사람을 홀리게 한다. 동방구문사기에 따르면 이 노래가 젊은층들 사이에서 인기가 있다고 한다. </Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag='TXT_KEY_UNIT_CJGG_RANGER_DESC'>
			<Text>산림감시원</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag='TXT_KEY_UNIT_CJGG_RANGER_HELP'>
			<Text>합성궁병을 대체합니다. 지형대응을 무시하며, 탄막 1 승급을 가집니다..</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag='TXT_KEY_UNIT_CJGG_RANGER_STRATEGY'>
			<Text>산림 보호 업무를 담당하는 농림축산식품부 산하기관. 1948년 11월 농림부 산림국으로 출발했으며, 1967년 1월 1일 산림청(4국 14과 1,083명)으로 독립했다. 1973년 3월 3일 내무부 소속으로 이관됐으며, 1987년 1월 1일 농림수산부 소속으로 다시 변경됐다. 1996년 8월 농림수산부가 농림부로 개칭함에 따라 농림부 소속 기관이 됐다가, 2013년 3월 23일 정부조직 개편으로 농림축산식품부 산하로 편제됐다.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag='TXT_KEY_UNIT_CJGG_RANGER_PEDIA'>
			<Text>국립수목원에 가서 맑은 공기를 실컷 마시고, 자연휴양림에 가서 편하게 쉬고... 우리가 이렇게 숲에서 즐거운 시간을 보낼 수 있는 것은 우리나라 전국 방방곡곡의 나무와 숲을 지키고 가꾸는 기관인 산림청 덕분이에요. 산림청은 나무와 숲 등 식물이 자라는 땅을 지키고 가꾸는 일을 해요. 산림청에서는 산림을 쓸모 있고 가치 있는 자원으로 만들려고 여러 노력을 기울이며, 산림 생태계가 무너지거나 훼손되지 않도록 꾸준히 나무와 숲을 관리해 국민에게 쉴 곳을 제공하지요.</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_ko_KR>
	<Language_ja_JP>
		<Row Tag='TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CJGG_ROCKCAFE_DESC'>
			<Text>ロックカフェ</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag='TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CJGG_ROCKCAFE_STRATEGY'>
			<Text>ハンバーガーを中心としたアメリカンレストランである。1971年6月14日、ロンドン在住のアメリカ人、アイザック・ティグレットとピーター・モートンによって設立された。アメリカ料理に馴染みがなかった欧州ですぐに話題になり、ロンドンの新名所になった。</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag='TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CJGG_ROCKCAFE_HELP'>
			<Text>鳥獣伎楽のUBです。オペラハウスを代替します</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag='TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CJGG_ROCKCAFE_PEDIA'>
			<Text>その後世界各国に展開し、現在では北アメリカ、ヨーロッパ、ラテンアメリカ、中近東、カリブ海、アジアなど世界の主要都市に120店舗以上がある。近年では、店舗の新規出店のほか、同じ都市の中での移転、撤退なども頻繁で、かつては店舗が存在したが現在は存在しない都市も多い。また、日本では例がなく、世界的にみても数は多くないが、カフェの他、ホテルやカジノの出店も行なっている。</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag='TXT_KEY_UNIT_CJGG_SINGER_DESC'>
			<Text>歌手</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag='TXT_KEY_UNIT_CJGG_SINGER_HELP'>
			<Text>斥候を代替します。コンサートツアーができ、陳腐化されません。</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag='TXT_KEY_UNIT_CJGG_SINGER_STRATEGY'>
			<Text>鳥の妖怪。袂雀（たもとすずめ）、あるいは鳥ではなく黒い蝶のようなもの、蛾の一種とも。雀のように「チッ、チッ、チッ」と鳴き声をあげながら夜に現れる妖怪で、山道を歩いている人の前後について来るという。 </Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag='TXT_KEY_UNIT_CJGG_SINGER_PEDIA'>
			<Text>
				種族は夜雀で歌う事と人間を襲う事が大好きな、自他ともに認めるお気楽妖怪。「歌で人を狂わせる程度の能力」を持つ。また、人間を鳥目にする(作中演出を信じるなら妖怪にも効く)ことも出来、これらの能力を使って夜道を一人で歩く人間を襲撃する。「妖怪には身体を食べるものと心を食べるものがいる」と多々良小傘が発言しているが、ミスティアがどちらに属するのかは不明。
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag='TXT_KEY_UNIT_CJGG_RANGER_DESC'>
			<Text>山林監視員</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag='TXT_KEY_UNIT_CJGG_RANGER_HELP'>
			<Text>戦闘弓射手を代替します。地形費用を無視し、一斉攻撃 I昇進を持ちます。</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag='TXT_KEY_UNIT_CJGG_RANGER_STRATEGY'>
			<Text>国有林野事業職員。国有林の管理・経営のため森林事務所に常駐する。フォレスター。</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag='TXT_KEY_UNIT_CJGG_RANGER_PEDIA'>
			<Text>環境省の地方支分部局である地方環境事務所に置かれる職、およびその職を任じられた人のことを呼ぶための用語である。行政用語としては日本語を用いるのが望ましいとの判断で「自然保護官」としたわけであるが、「自然保護官」ではいささか固いので、日常的には米国などに倣って「レンジャー」と呼ばれることもある。</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_ja_JP>
</GameData>